{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_7_3RM1LD",
                "player_3_3RM1LD",
                "player_9_3RM1LD",
                "player_4_3RM1LD",
                "player_6_3RM1LD",
                "player_16_3RM1LD"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                7,
                3,
                9,
                4,
                6,
                16
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "stand",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    15671.436,
                    -733.562,
                    -12708.725,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    15566.257,
                    -958.748,
                    -12708.725,
                    0,
                    75.44672791512599,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    15396.548,
                    -1123.971,
                    -12708.725,
                    0,
                    122.20839984289717,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    15282.083,
                    -1194.908,
                    -12708.725,
                    0,
                    53.988359229109506,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    15301.687,
                    -1357.086,
                    -12708.725,
                    0,
                    130.25239097054168,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    15305.731,
                    -865.556,
                    -12708.725,
                    0,
                    -29.948049416409646,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            15452.871,
            -1550.496,
            -12708.725
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1045.666494299615
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            15196.971,
            -514.612,
            -12708.725,
            0,
            -66.90053212084182,
            0
        ],
        [
            15276.27,
            -1860.807,
            -12708.725,
            0,
            80.03773652531416,
            0
        ],
        [
            15198.119,
            -1237.426,
            -12708.725,
            0,
            41.73009414379185,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are observed in a non-standing position in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Excluding the individuals with light skin color, how many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are either bald or wearing a fedora hat?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Among the individuals who are not wearing glasses, how many are women?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many human figures are visible that are not bald and are also not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "five"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-neck top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. running",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "B. standing"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the navy blue polo shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. picking up"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouching"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the white and blue floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. kneeling",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "B. standing"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. picking up"
                ],
                "answer": "C. standing"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. picking up",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouching"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V-top relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V-top relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}